* * Explore
        
        Right Caret Icon
        
        Left Caret Icon
        
        * Why the Army

            Service Options

            About

        Switch between site languages:
        
        En
        
        Esp

        Close Icon
        
    * Army Life
        
        Right Caret Icon
        
        Left Caret Icon
        
        * What to Expect

            Training

            Daily Life

        Switch between site languages:
        
        En
        
        Esp

        Close Icon
        
    * Careers & Jobs
        
        Right Caret Icon
        
        Left Caret Icon
        
        * Career Paths

            College Path

            Medical Path

            Specialized Paths

            Special Operations

            Career Development

        Switch between site languages:
        
        En
        
        Esp

        Close Icon
        
    * Benefits
        
        Right Caret Icon
        
        Left Caret Icon
        
        * While Serving

            After Serving

        Switch between site languages:
        
        En
        
        Esp

        Close Icon
        
    * How to Join
        
        Right Caret Icon
        
        Left Caret Icon
        
        * Process

            Qualifications

            Test Your Readiness

        Switch between site languages:
        
        En
        
        Esp

        Close Icon
        
* Switch between site languages:
    
    En
    
    Esp

* Bookmark Icon
    
* Search Icon
    
    Search Icon
    
    Close Icon
    
    Error: Please try again later
    
    Submit Search
    
    Recent Searches
    
    Most Frequently Searched

    Suggested Searches
    
    Close Icon

Close Icon

Menu Icon

Privacy & Security
==================

U.S. Army privacy & security policy
-----------------------------------

### Communications agreement and opt-out

When you agree to be contacted by the United States Army, communications with you may be via mail, telephone, text message, e-mail, social media, and other electronic messages unless you opt-out or revoke your consent. By checking the applicable box, and submitting your personal information, you explicitly agree with all information outlined below on this page.  
  
You may opt-out or revoke consent to receive communications from the United States Army at any time. To opt-out of email communication from the United States Army, go to [https://www.goarmy.com/a/optout/global/(Opens in new window)](https://www.goarmy.com/a/optout/global). To revoke consent to receive SMS (text message) communication from the United States Army, a user must reply “STOP” to an SMS message generated by the United States Army. To revoke consent to receive phone calls from the United States Army, call 1-800-USA-ARMY or advise the United States Army representative calling you.

### United States Army Event Waiver and Release of Liability

The “United States Army Event Waiver and Release of Liability” section is for individuals using the GoArmy.com website to register for attendance in a U.S. Army activity. You must be at least 16 years old and complete all the information requested in order to participate.  
  
I, Participant, on behalf of myself and my heirs, successors and assigns, hereby agree that in connection with my participation in the United States Army special event or other interactive activities (collectively, the "Event") fully and forever release, waive, discharge, and agree not to sue the United States Army or its event marketing and advertising agencies, its Event producers, other participants, sponsoring and participating organizations, the owners and lessees of the premises and/or equipment used to conduct the Event and the respective agents, officers directors and employees of each of the foregoing (collectively, the "Releasees") for any and all claims, causes of action or liability of any kind, including claims, causes of action or liability for any injury (including death), loss or damages sustained or incurred by me (or my property) arising out of or in any way associated with my participation in the Event including all claims, causes of action or liability arising out of the negligence of any of the Releasees.  
  
I acknowledge that I have voluntarily chosen to assume all risks associated with my participation in the Event, both known and unknown, including those risks that result from the negligence of the Releasees or others and assume full responsibility for my participation in the Event.  
  
I understand that the Event may be photographed, videotaped, or otherwise recorded, and I agree that the United States Army and its agents, designees and licensees may use my name and likeness (in any form and without regard to any alteration) in photographs, videotapes, audiotapes, and any and all other media, throughout the world, in perpetuity, without any additional consideration to me or to any third party. I shall have no right of approval and no legal claim arising out of any use or editing of my name and likeness. The United States Army and its agents, designees and licensees shall have no obligation to use any of the rights I grant.

### GoArmy.com privacy policy & security notice

The United States Army and GoArmy.com are committed to protecting your privacy. We use security technology and security procedures to protect your personal information and your privacy. This section outlines information we collect, how it is used, and how you can opt out of data collection. This includes personal information collected on request forms and activity on GoArmy.com website.

When you contact us, we will collect personal information about you so that we may contact you and best respond to your request. Disclosure of personal information by you is strictly voluntary. You are under no obligation whatsoever to provide a United States Army representative any information. All information collected will be used strictly for recruiting purposes. The authority for the collection of this information is Title 10; United States Code; Section 503.

We may use information you provide to determine your qualifications, to improve your GoArmy.com experience, and to personalize information we send you.

GoArmy.com uses Cookies to track activity on GoArmy.com by default. Cookies are pieces of text placed on your electronic device that store information regarding your use of that site. Cookies help the United States Army better understand customer needs, personalize, and customize user experience, and continuously improve the website. Cookies allow better analysis of the effectiveness of GoArmy.com pages and the United States Army marketing efforts. Dynamic IP address may also be used for the purposes of media attribution, and is not collected and retained by the US Army. The Army uses employs the use of “multi-session” cookies, which may be stored for a period of up to 12 months. These technologies may be used to collect information about your online activities, enable performance attribution of Army marketing activities, and when using our online services to further personalize your experience with us. Cookies do not collect or store Personally Identifiable Information (PII) such as name, address, phone or email. Cookies do not give U.S. Army servers access to your device. By using the GoArmy.com website, you explicitly consent to the United States Army using Cookies to track your activity on GoArmy.com. Users can choose not to accept the use of these cookies by changing the settings on their local computer's web browser. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies. The USA.gov website, [https://www.usa.gov/optout-instructions(Opens in new window)](https://www.usa.gov/optout-instructions), provides general instructions on how to opt out of cookies and other commonly used Web measurement and customization technologies. Opting out of cookies still permits users to access comparable information and services; however, you may not be able to take full advantage of the Website if you do so. Additionally, it may take longer to navigate or interact with the website if a user is required to fill out certain information repeatedly.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by visiting the [Digital Advertising Alliance website(Opens in new window)](https://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN), [US Gov Opt-Out website(Opens in new window)](https://www.usa.gov/optout-instructions) or the [Network Advertising Initiative website(Opens in new window)](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1). If you choose to opt out, you will continue to receive advertisements but they will not be tailored to your interests.

The United States Army uses software programs and analytics tools to collect and analyze statistical data about your activity on GoArmy.com. This data is used to improve user experience on goarmy.com, understand web traffic patterns, identify opportunities to improve the overall quality of the site, as well as, for advertising and marketing.

The United States Army may use third-party service providers, as well as their software programs and analytical tools, to collect and analyze statistical data about your activity on GoArmy.com. The United States Army may share internet usage or other de-identified information with third-party service providers if you save a job on GoArmy.com, but the United States Army will not share any Personally Identifiable Information (PII) with third-party service providers. For example, we may use third parties to help us manage ads on other sites, or assist with data storage. Internet usage or other de-identified data may be shared with third parties to enable tasks only for the purposes we've authorized, and we require them to provide at least the same level of protection for your information as maintained by the Army Privacy Policy. We may also share with third parties aggregated or anonymized information that does not directly identify you. For example, we may share anonymous, aggregated statistics about your use of our online services. Or we may combine information about you with other users and share the information in a way that does not link to a specific user. By using the GoArmy.com website, you explicitly consent to third-party data sharing. The USA.gov website, [https://www.usa.gov/optout-instructions(Opens in new window)](https://www.usa.gov/optout-instructions), provides general instructions on how to opt out of cookies and other commonly used Web measurement and customization technologies.

For site security purposes, this government computer system employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this service are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act.

The GoArmy.com Privacy Impact Assessment (PIA) can be [found by clicking this link](https://www.goarmy.com/content/dam/goarmy/files/Army-PIA-form.pdf "Click to download Privacy Impact Assessment form").

GoArmy.com System of Record Notice (SORN) ID is A0601-210c TRADOC and can be [found by clicking this link(Opens in new window)](https://dpcld.defense.gov/Privacy/SORNsIndex/DOD-wide-SORN-Article-View/Article/570073/a0601-210c-tradoc).

### Marketing SMS terms & conditions

**Program Name:** U.S. Army SMS Recruitment  
**  
Program Description:** By subscribing to the U.S. Army SMS Recruitment, you will receive approximately up to two marketing SMS messages per week containing information about joining the U.S. Army, career opportunities, benefits, events, news, and other updates related to military service.  
**  
Cancellation and Opt-Out:** You can opt out or cancel your consent to receive SMS messages at any time. Just text "STOP" to the short code number. Once you send "STOP", we may send you an SMS reply to confirm that you have been unsubscribed, and you will no longer receive SMS messages from us. If you wish to re-subscribe in the future, you can sign up again as you did initially.  
**  
Support:** If you experience any issues with the messaging program, reply with the keyword "HELP" to the short code number for assistance, or contact our support team at support@aemo.goarmy.com.

You acknowledge and agree the Cancellation/Opt-Out and Support methods are reasonable to revoke consent for SMS messages.  
**  
Cost and Carrier Disclaimer:** U.S. Army SMS Recruitment will never charge for the text messages you receive. Message and data rates may apply in accordance with the terms of your cellular subscription plan. Other carrier-specific rates may apply, depending on your individual wireless pricing plan, in accordance with your wireless customer agreement. You are responsible for all applicable taxes. Carriers are not liable for delayed or undelivered messages. If you have any questions about your text plan or data plan, please contact your wireless service provider.  
**  
Message Frequency:** You will receive approximately up to two marketing SMS messages per week.   
**  
Privacy Policy:** Your privacy is important to us, for information regarding our privacy practices, please refer to our Privacy Policy at [https://www.goarmy.com/privacy.html.](https://www.goarmy.com/privacy.html. "https://www.goarmy.com/privacy.html.")

Your wireless carrier and other service providers may collect data about your SMS usage, and their practices are governed by their own privacy policies. You acknowledge and agree that the SMS Service is provided via wireless systems which use radios (and other means) to transmit communications over complex networks. We do not guarantee that your use of the SMS Service will be private or secure, and we are not liable to you for any lack of privacy or security you may experience. You are fully responsible for taking precautions and providing security measures best suited for your situation and intended use of the SMS Service.  
  
By subscribing to the U.S. Army SMS Recruitment, you agree to these Terms and Conditions.

### Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) office

Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) ensures public access to U.S. government records. The FOIA office is responsible for management oversight of the implementation of FOIA Act programs in accordance with 5 USC, and Public Law 106-554.

### GoArmy.com website copyright

The United States Army Recruiting web site (GoArmy.com) is provided as a public service by the Army Enterprise Marketing Office (AEMO) and the Department of the Army. Information presented on the Army Recruiting web site is considered public information and may be distributed or copied. Photographs, videos and music require permission for use and remain the property of the United States Army or copyright owner and may not be reproduced except by permission.

### Medical disclaimer

The United States Army may offer fitness information designed for educational purposes only. You should not rely on this information as a substitute for, nor does it replace, professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. If you have any concerns or questions about your health, you should always consult with a physician or other health-care professional. You should consult your physician or other health care professional before starting any fitness program to determine if it is right for your needs. Do not start any fitness program if your physician or health care provider advises against it. If you experience faintness, dizziness, pain or shortness of breath at any time while exercising you should stop immediately. Do not disregard, avoid or delay obtaining medical or health related advice from your health-care professional because of something you may have read on this site. The use of any information provided on this site is solely at your own risk.

### Accessibility statement

The United States Army is dedicated to making all information and technology available to individuals with disabilities. In 1998, Section 508 of the Rehabilitation Act Amendments, as amended by the Workforce Investment Act of 1998, issued accessibility standards setting forth electronic and information technology performance criteria. As amended, Section 508 requires that when Federal agencies develop, procure, maintain, or use electronic and information technology, they must ensure that this information is accessible to every individual.

### Contact information

The Army Enterprise Marketing Office  
11 W. Quincy Ct.  
Chicago, IL 60604

Footer
------

* ### Site Links
    
    * #### Teams & Events
        
    * #### Support
        
    * #### Legal
        
* ### Site Information
    
    * #### Social Media Links
        
        Connect
        
    * #### Phone Number

Get In Touch

*  

My Jobs
-------

You have no saved jobs.

Take a short quiz or explore more than 200 jobs that might interest you.

### Tell us about yourself.

All fields are required.

MAC:

Activity Title:

GoArmy Title:

 MAC Please enter a MAC

 First Name Please enter a First Name Last Name Please enter a Last Name  Birth Date Please enter a Birth Date  Email Address Please enter an Email Address  Phone Number Please enter a Phone Number  ZIP Code Please enter a ZIP Code

### Now, who referred you?

Fill in the first and last names of the person who referred you, along with their Department of Defense identification number (DoD ID #) for proof of service and phone number if they want to receive status updates. Their information is protected and maintained by the [Privacy & Security Notice](https://www.goarmy.com/privacy)

 First Name Please enter DoD agent's First Name Last Name Please enter DoD agent's Last Name  DoD ID # Please enter DoD agent's ID  Phone Number (Optional) Please enter DoD agent's Phone Number

#### Choose the Army career path you’re most interested in.

Full-Time Service

Weekend & Part-Time Service

Health Care Students & Professionals

Leadership Training for College (ROTC)

### Answer True or False to the following statements based on your current situation (optional).

#### I’m a U.S. citizen or permanent and legal resident (I-551 card).

True

False

#### I am in high school, have a high school diploma, or am enrolled in college.

True

False

#### I have a GED.

True

False

#### I don’t have any tattoos.

True

False

#### I have some tattoos, with no (or subtle) placement on my hands, neck, or face.

True

False

#### I don’t have any medical concerns.

True

False

#### I have a minor medical condition or history.

True

False

#### I don’t have any law violations.

True

False

#### I have minor law violations, like speeding tickets.

True

False

#### I’m ready to talk to a recruiter to learn more.

True

False

#### I’m interested in the Army, but not quite ready to talk to a recruiter.

True

False

### Find ROTC programs at schools you’re most interested in.

This helps us connect you to the right person. If you’re not sure yet, just select undecided.

Find ROTC programs at schools you’re most interested in.

State

School Name

School selection is required.

By checking this box and submitting this form, I agree to receive email communications from the U.S. Army. I verify this is my mobile number and consent to being contacted by individual recruiters via text. I also agree to the [Waiver & Release of Liability and the Privacy Policy](https://www.goarmy.com/privacy). Message and Data rates may apply.

I consent to receiving up to two automated marketing texts per week from the U.S. Army. Message and data rates may apply. Text HELP for support, STOP to opt out. See the [Privacy Policy](https://www.goarmy.com/privacy). (Optional)

Get More Information

Privacy Act Notice: The above disclosure is voluntary. All information will be used strictly for recruiting purposes. The authority for the collection of this information is Title 10, United States Code, Sections 503, 505, 508, and 12102, and EO 9397. For more information, please review our [Privacy & Security Notice.](https://www.goarmy.com/privacy)

Recent entries.

Give us a call
--------------

Contact your local recruiting office with any questions.
